So, I'll just leave that, thank you so much again
for having this, you know, this is very dangerous.
You know, we don't work for companies
that have billions of dollars.
You know, we're running and gunning often on our own.
A lot, we became friends, a lot of us are friends
because we wouldn't see each other all the time
and we became friends because we wanted
to have someone watch our back while we're out there
because like I said, we're just out there.
And, but we'll continue to do it
because it's an important topic, it's an important issue.
The American people deserve to know what's happening
in these chaotic situations and, you know,
we're more than happy to do it.
So, thanks, sir.
Great job, thank you very much, very much.
Katie, please.